# Edoardo Tedesco

Data Physicist



### Profile

My name is Edoardo, I am 24 years old and I have a degree in Physics from the Department of Physics in Milan. I am currently continuing my studies in Data Physics, following my broader interest in data science. I am particularly passionate about the business world and innovation.

#### Education

2023 – Master's Degree in Physics LM-17, Department of Physics, Milan, Specialization: Data ongoing Physics

2020 – 2021 Startup Certificate for Young Aspiring Entrepreneurs, Lions Club International District LIONS

2018–2023 Bachelor's Degree in Physics L-30, Department of Physics, Milan

Oct 2014–Jul Scientific Diploma, Liceo Scientifico Donatelli Pascal

2018

# Experience

2019–2023 Math and Physics Teacher, Didattica Athena

2021 Computer Science Teacher, Centro Studi Milano

2017–2018 Technical Laborer and Worker, La Regina del Pomodoro s.r.l.

## Skills

Great Reader, Critical Thinking, Communication, Time Management, Team Player, Fast Learner

## Research

2023+ Thesis, A New Application for Extinction Maps Production (Astronomy, Computer Science, Molecolar Clouds, Data Anlaysis) Supervisor: M. Lombardi

#### Certifications

2022 First Certificate in English (FCE) - Cambridge B2 Level

### Languages

English B2

Italian Native Speaker

# Coding

Python Proficient

C++ Intermediate